

# **ENES BAYAR**

## WEB DEVELOPER

☑ lenesbayar@gmail.com



0552 231 2086

## **EDUCATION**

Selcuk University Computer Engineer 2020 - 2024

## **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- React.js
- C#
- Unity
- Flutter

## **LANGUAGES**

• English B1 level

## **INFORMATIONS**

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin. com/in/enesbayarr/

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/e nbayy

## **HOBBIES**

Chess

## **ABOUT ME**

After my experiences in the field of game development I turned to the field of web development again. My basic skills by expanding web technologies such as HTML, CSS and JavaScript while learning, the creative approach I gained in the gaming world and Opportunity to apply your problem solving skills to your web projects I found. To improve user experience and be aesthetically appealing I use my game development experience to create designs. I maintained my aesthetic approach and detail-oriented way of thinking. This Change has been an exciting learning process for me

## **WORK HISTORY**

### **GAME DEVELOPER INTERN**

El-Capitan Game - Oct 2023 - Feb 2024

• I gained valuable experience in the mobile game development process. During this period, he worked on different mobile game projects and compilation of both mechanics and user experience I developed an understanding. Additionally, advertising integration into games Focusing on advertising revenue optimization and user I worked on interaction. In this process, both my technical skills I also had the opportunity to improve my communication skills and Experience the dynamcis in the gaming industry more closely I got lucky.

#### WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

BSK Information Technologies - Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

• By designing various websites and using JavaScript to create them I gained valuable experience by adding interactive elements. The websites I design have user-frendly interfaces. While gaining a modern and functional appearance, using JavaScript I increased the user experience by making the applications more interactive. While working on websites, both design and coding I had the opportuntly to constantly improve myself in the field and this experience It helped me advance further in the field of web development.